Ruan Vítor Elpídio

Brazilian - 19 years - Single

Phone Number: (+55) 31 99491-8770

Address: Belo Horizonte, MG - Brazil

E-mail: ruanvelpidio@hotmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/RuanDevJs

Goal

I have two years of experience on TypeScript, React and Node.js, where I enhance them by creating complexity systems, websites and API's. Besides that, I have good communication, listening and ability to guide customers meeting due my last job, where I had help after sales team (doing meets 1:1 with customers and control the progress of some project), besides fix complexity projects, create new features, E2E tests using Vue.js and Cypress, create new routes, fix old codes from API using Ruby on Rails and Node.js.

Education

- Software Engineering | FIAP University (Brazil) | 2023 Present Days
- High School | COTEMIG Technical School in Informatics (Brazil) | 2020 2021

Technologies Stacks

Basic Web Development – HTML, CSS, JavaScript (ES6) and WordPress.

Front End Frameworks – React, Next.js, Vue.js, Quasar, Cypress and Firebase.

Back End Development – Node.js, PHP7, Ruby on Rails, MySQL, PostgreSQL and MongoDB.

Mobile Development – React Native and TypeScript.

Work Experience

Speed IO (January 2022 – August 2023) | Remote

Position: Mid-Level Front-End Developer

Services Provided: Create new features for API (creating new routes in REST pattern) using Node.js and Ruby on Rails, fix old codes, fix bugs, add features using Vue.js and test them using Cypress.

Verticis Webstudio (June 2021 – December 2021) | Hybrid

Position: Web Development Intern

Services Provided: Create features like add integration with Google ADS, maintenance and create websites (landing pages, e-commerce and institutional websites) using WordPress, PHP and JavaScript.

LANGUAGES

English Level B2 | Number One (Castelo Branch, Brazil) | 2018 - 2020